Achmad Sufyan Aziz

Front End Engineer

085211181046 achmadsufyan98@gmail.com https://asufyanaziz.vercel.app/ Jakarta Selatan, DKI Jakarta

SUMMARY

A Front End Engineer with more than 1 year experience in writing programs using React with Javascript or TypeScript. I have experience developing and improving web applications with rules of following performance limits, system design, and user acceptance, and also I have good skills to analyze problems in a program. I am committed to learning and testing myself with something new such as making the program more efficient and professional

EXPERIENCE

03/2022 - Present

Junior Front End Engineer

Waresix

Fleet Management Team (November 2022 - Present)

- Develop, improve, and maintain features related to fleet management for internal users
- Develop, improve, and maintain features related to trip, fleet management, and payment management for vendor users
- Improve the style of component system design for a newer look
- · Create unit test
- Fixing bug

Payment Management Team (March 2022 - September 2022)

- Develop, improve, and maintain features related to payment management for internal users
- Improve component system design so that it can be adjusted to the needs of the payment management team
- Fixing bug

11/2021 - 02/2022

Intern Junior Front End Engineer

Waresix

- Front End design, development and testing using React to build feature-rich and user-friendly web applications.
- Develop, test and maintain responsive web apps with elegant UX that delight users and raise their productivity.
- Develop features related to payment management for internal users
- Fixing bug

01/2021 - 09/2021

Intern Web Developer

Badan Pengembangan Teknologi Informasi (BPTI) - UHAMKA

· Create website sipesat (sistem pengajuan surat) using React.js and Node.js

07/2020 - 09/2020

Web Developer

Freelance

Front End - React.js

- Maintance web appointment dentist (docpro)
- Create a few features on the website (docpro)

Back End - Node.js

• Create API web appointment dentist(docpro)

EDUCATION

2022 Computer Engineering

Uhamka

Bachelor Degree

2016 Science Major

Al-Hamidiyah Madrasah Aliyah

• Remaja Masjid as Humas (Deputy Coordinator)

CERTIFICATES

07/2022 - Present JavaScript (Intermediate) Certificate

06/2022 - Present JavaScript (Basic) Certificate

06/2022 - Present CSS Certificate

06/2022 - Present React (Basic) Certificate

08/2019 - Present React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux)

SKILLS

HTML/CSS Advanced **Typescript** Intermediate SCSS Advanced Node.js Intermediate React.js Advanced GIT Intermediate Agile (Scrum) Javascript Intermediate Intermediate

LANGUAGES

Indonesia Native English Intermediate